https://www.easton.com/easton-support/legal/privacy-policy.html

Fastpitch
All Fastpitch
Bats
All Bats
ASA & USSSA (Dual Stamp)
ASA/USA
ASA & USSSA (Dual Stamp)
Questions and Feedback
The Company is committed to respecting the privacy and security of your personal information. The following U.S. online privacy policy describes the information we collect and how we use it. By using this Web Site, you consent to our privacy policy.
For questions or concerns, please email us at legal@easton.com or contact us at:
Easton Diamond Sports, LLC .
Attention: Legal Department
3500 Willow Lane
Thousand Oaks, CA 91361
1.818.902.5824
Collecting Information
Like many web sites, we gather information about how visitors use our Web Site. In general, you can visit many of our web pages without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself. We may track your visit for trends and statistics, but you will remain anonymous unless you tell us who you are. Once you choose to give us your personal information, you are not anonymous to us.
We may collect personal information when you register on, log on, or visit our Web Sites, including when you purchase products and services, participate in activities on our Web Sites, such as sweepstakes, contests, games, and informational and promotional offers, and when you provide information to our customer service representatives. Finally, our Web Sites may offer message boards, conversation pages, chat rooms, social community environments, profile pages, and other Public Forums (as defined in the Terms of Use governing our Web Sites (the "Terms")), as well as other features in which you may provide us with User Generated Materials (as defined in the Terms). If you provide personal information when you use any of these features, that personal information may be publicly posted and otherwise disclosed without limitation as to its use by a third party.  We may use third parties to provide products, services and information to you.  These service providers will have access to your personal information in order to provide these services, but when this occurs we implement reasonable contractual and technical protections to limit their use of that information to helping us provide the service.
In order to better understand your preferences and better serve you, we may combine information you give us online with other information from the Company's sources, transactions and communications. This may include data from the Company's online marketing. We may also combine that information with data that is publicly available and data that we receive from other reputable sources. This data may include postal address updates and demographic data. We collect information to respond to customer service inquiries and for analysis purposes only. All data combined and stored with online data is protected by this privacy policy.
Online Behavioral Advertising Disclosure
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web Site. These companies may use information about your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please visit http://www.networkadvertising.org/.
The third-party that provides this service for us is Conversant.  To opt out of Converstant's data collection and advertisement services, please click here.
Tracking Mechanisms and Deletion of Cookies
We collect non-personal information about our Web Site traffic and usage patterns from technology such as Cookies and Web Beacons. "Cookies" are small text files that help us to personalize the content of our Web Site. "Web Beacons" are electronic files used to track your navigation on a Web Site or collection of Web Sites, the completion of transactions, submittal of applications and browsing behavior.
We use cookies and other tracking technology to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits, and keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about Web Site traffic and Web Site interaction so that we can offer better Web Site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our Web Site visitors. These service providers are permitted to use the information collected on our behalf to help us conduct and improve our business.
If you prefer, you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. However, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a Cookie is being sent or you can choose to turn off all Cookies. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your Cookie settings. If you turn Cookies off, you won't have access to many features that make your Web Site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly.
We also use pixel tags (tiny graphic images) to help us analyze your online behavior. Pixel tags also allow us to send you email in a format you can read and let us know when you have opened an email message from us.
We may use pixel tags to collect information about your visit, including the pages you view, the links you click and other actions taken in connection with our Web Sites and services. Through pixel tags, we also collect certain standard information that your browser sends to every web site you visit, such as your IP address, browser type and language, access times and referring web site addresses.
Description of the Type of Online Data Collected, How it is Used/Transferred, and Opt-Out
Non-Personally Identifiable Information: When you visit the Web Site, we collect some basic information that does not identify individual users. This includes pages visited, types of products purchased, and feedback from our visitors, as well as location data, logs and other communication data, and information about your computer and internet connection, including your IP address, operating system and browser type. We then aggregate this information with other pieces of information to improve our Web Site and make your experience on the Web Site as valuable and efficient as possible. Pages of the Web Site may use devices that permit us to count users who have visited those pages and for other related Web Site statistics (for example, recording the popularity of certain Web Site content and verifying system and server integrity).
Third party advertising companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. These third party cookies do not collect personally identifiable information. For more information about cookies and how to opt out of third party data collection, please see the "Offline/Online Data Use/Transfer and Opt-Out" Section of this policy.
As indicated, Conversant is a third-party service provider that serves ads to you on our behalf.  To opt out of Converstant's data collection and advertisement services, please click here.
Personally Identifiable Information: If you purchase an item online from us or interact with our Web Site by submitting feedback, joining a mailing list, or writing a product review, you provide us or our third-party service providers with information including:
• First and last name
• Billing address
• Shipping address(es)
• Email address
• Phone number
• Credit card account number
Offline/Online Data Use/Transfer and Opt-Out:
For Advertisers that are not transferring offline data
We may share your non-personal information to deliver tailored advertising to you that match your interests when you visit our Web Site as well as other Web Sites.
You may opt-out of the use of your information for tailored advertising purposes. To learn more about the use of this information or to choose not to have this information used by our third-party advertising partner by opting out, please visit the Network Advertising Initiative by clicking here. If you delete your Cookies, use a different browser, or buy a new computer, you will need to renew your opt-out choice.
As indicated, Conversant is a third-party service provider that serves ads to you on our behalf.  To opt out of Converstant's data collection and advertisement services, please click here.
For Advertisers that are transferring offline data:
We may share your personally identifiable information and non-personal information, including your name, address, email address, and any transactions you conduct on our Web Site or offline with us with a third party advertising partner and its service providers in order to deliver tailored advertising to you that matches your interests when you visit our Web Site and other Web Sites. Our advertising partner will make the data that we provide anonymous, so no one else will receive your personally identifiable information.
You may opt-out of the use of your information for tailored advertising purposes. To learn more about the use of this information or to choose not to have this information used by our third-party advertising partner by opting out, please visit the Network Advertising Initiative by clicking here. If you delete your Cookies, use a different browser, or buy a new computer, you will need to renew your opt-out choice.
As indicated, Conversant is a third-party service provider that serves ads to you on our behalf.  To opt out of Converstant's data collection and advertisement services, please click here.
Using Information
We may use the information we collect to:
• Customize and/or personalize your communications
• Process and/or fulfill your order requests
• Better respond to your customer service inquiries
• Communicate with you about our products and events, and for other promotional purposes
• Improve our business
• Administer contests, promotions, surveys or other Web Site features
* Please note that we have the ability to retain any data that you provide on this Web Site, even if you do not complete your registration or transaction by clicking submit or next. Such contact details and data may be used to contact you to inquire why you did not complete your registration or transaction.
Sharing Information
We may provide your information to the Company's wholly-owned companies and affiliates, which may be outside the U.S. For the purpose of operating our business, we may transfer information between the Company and our third party service providers who use that information only to conduct the Company's business. For example, they may handle the Company's credit card processing, shipping, data management, email distribution, market research, information analysis, and promotions management. We provide our preferred service providers with the information they need to perform their services and work with them to respect and protect your information. We do not provide your personally identifiable information to any third parties for their own marketing purposes.
On rare occasions, we may disclose specific information upon governmental request, in response to a court order, when required by law, regulation, subpoena or legal process, to enforce our Web Site policies including investigation of potential violations, to detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or to protect our or others' rights, property, or safety. We may also share information with companies assisting in any of the above purposes. We do not provide information to these agencies or companies for marketing or commercial purposes.
Protecting Information
We use a variety of security measures, including commercially reasonable encryption and authentication tools to maintain the safety of your personal information. Your personal information is contained behind secure networks and is only accessible to a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. When you place orders or access your personal information, we offer the use of a secure server. All credit card information you supply is transmitted to a third party service provider via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. Regardless of these efforts, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.
Children's Privacy
We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. The Company believes that parents should supervise their children's online activities and consider using parental control tools available from online services and software manufacturers that help provide a child-friendly online environment. These tools can also prevent children from disclosing online their name, address and other personal information without parental permission.
Policy Changes
We may change our privacy policy from time to time. We encourage you to refer to this policy on an ongoing basis so that you understand our current privacy policy.
Questions and Feedback
We welcome your questions, comments, and concerns about privacy. Please send us any and all feedback pertaining to privacy, or any other issue to legal@easton.com.
